Guide to the Charles Bockelman, Associate Provost, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Charles Bockelman, associate provost, Yale University, records
1968-1978
RU 791
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
(2 boxes)
The records consist of subject files maintained by Charles Bockelman as associate provost of Yale.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Bockelman, Charles
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Provost, 1992.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files maintained by Charles Bockelman as associate provost of Yale.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records of Charles Bockelman as associate provost, 1968-1978; Accession 1992-A-059
  - Associated universities, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative action plan (Box 1)
  - A-21, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Ascuitto, R., 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Kingman, 1967-1973 (Box 1)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1974-1977 (Box 1)
  - Computer center, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Computation management board, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Computer center operation committee, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Carnegie Mellon University visting committee, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Development office, 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - Diller project, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - EDUCOM, 1976-1978 (Box 1)
  - EDUCOM (cont'd), 1970-1977 (Box 2)
  - Education coach '72 enrollments, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
  - Executive committee of the faculty of arts and sciences, 1970-1976 (Box 2)
  - Grants and contracts, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
  - Grant and contract administration, 1975-1978 (Box 2)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School, 1975-1978 (Box 2)
  - Indirect costs, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Shool, 1975-1978 (Box 2)
  - Haskins Laboratories, 1968-1974 (Box 2)
  - Medical School plans, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - School of Medicine, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - National Science Foundation - physics panel, 1972-1973 (Box 2)